Who hasn't recorded a script at some point in their life?
That is why we have created Table Read Tools,
a new way of looking at your scripts.
First of all, we assign an image to each character.
Then you arrange them by importance.
That's good.
Then we go to locations
and add the locations.
Here is one.
And the next one.
And once you have everything ready, we move to the conversation module.
From now on, you can see your scripts as if they were a chat conversation.
It shows you the character who is speaking and the script time elapsed.
Or you can view it as a script reading.
You see the space where the scene takes place and then
Let the magic happen by itself.
The dialogues automatically move from one character to another
with an approximate calculation of the time needed for someone to read them.
You can run it automatically or move forward manually.
You can export the photographs to apply them to other projects if you have the same actors
And that's it, a new way of looking at your scripts.